Luis Campuzano

campuzano.luis10@gmail.com | (551) 265-7833 | Tampa, FL | https://www.linkedin.com/in/luis-campuzano-45164a86 | Portfolio: https://lcampuzano10.github.jo/LuisCampuzano/

OBJECTIVE

Results-driven C# .Net Software Developer with more than 3 years of programming seeking a position where I can use those gained skills with challenge problem-solving and create solutions. Build more than 7 Windows Programs and Consoles Applications as well as more than 4 ASP.NET MVC and .Net Core Websites. Knowledge of Microsoft SQL Server, Entity Framework, and Visual Studio. A strong academic background in the IT field, and workforce from an IT Specialist thru experienced Help Desk Supervisor.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, University of South Florida, Tampa, FL

Graduated May 2020

- Associate in Science in Information Technology, Bergen Community College, Paramus, NJ

2011 - 2014

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Highly proficient in development systems using C# language.
- Expertise in operating Visual Studio .NET for testing and debugging systems
- Proficient in ASP.NET, .NET Framework 4.6/4.7.1, .NET Core 2.2, 3.0, 3.1, IIS 7.0
- Proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, JSON, RESTful API, LINQ, JQUERY
- Proficient on Azure DevOps (TFS) using Git commands and VS Team Explorer
- Proficient in Database Design using SQL Server, Project Lifecycle Development, and QA testing
- Well versed in working with Linux, Windows operating systems on PC and Servers, as well as Office 2016 and 2019
- Skilled at working with web services of SOAP, JSON and XML
- Knowledge of Angular 6+ Framework and TypeScript.
- Knowledge of AWS EC2, AWS CloudFormation, AWS S3, AWS Elastic Beanstalk, AWS RDS, AWS Route 53, Scrum, RDBMS, MySQL
- Knowledge of Google Maps API, Twilio API.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, Tenex, Tampa, FL

Jun 2020 - Present

I joined Tenex as a Software Developer in June 2020. While there I'm in training understanding their large software modules. How to participate and contribute to design and development of user experience. Also, in training to participate in the full software lifecycle of web-based and mobile solutions with an emphasis on complex coding activities and keeping up with changing user requirements and fast paced agile development cycles.

Primary Responsibilities

- Work with a team of around 20 developers using Azure DevOps (TFS) for committing my changes
- Work on small assigned tasks via Board on Azure DevOps
- Fixed bug issues by reading and fixing JavaScript code.
- Fixed bug issues by reading and fixing Visual Basic .Net code.
- Work with MySQL Databases for creating and editing query and store procedures

Software Developer, Mid Atlantic Finance, Clearwater, FL

Jul 2016 - March 2020

I joined Mid Atlantic Finance as an IT Help Desk in July 2016. From July 2017 to June 2019 I worked as an Entry Level .NET C# Developer, then as .NET Developer until March 2020. This experience has enriched my knowledge in designing and developing applications with .NET framework while giving me an opportunity of working on projects with different departments such as Finance, Collection and IT within others.

Primary Responsibilities

- Study the requirements of the clients and the specific needs of the business projects
- Design, develop and implement web applications, based on .NET applications
- Customize the developed applications as per the client specifications
- Test the developed applications using the various tests tools and performance metrics
- Debug the web applications to rectify the errors that surface during the operations
- Adhere to the .NET protocols and standards set for developing the applications
- Draft a logical series of instructions as program codes to determine the software's communication

PROJECTS

• Developed a website project using ASP.NET MVC where it searches on the database using Entity Framework where the page it is split on two website so the user can search two different accounts at the same time, then will merge both accounts in one based on the user criteria, saving bites on the database and user time by searching next time for only one account.

- Developed a website project using ASP.NET MVC where it searches on the database using Entity Framework for a range of
 accounts, calculate the rating using a library created by another developer and shows on a table the information acquired, once the
 user updates the rating will write back to another table, also I was in charge to deploy it to our IIS Server.
- Developed a window form application on C# where users can see, select, and extract a zip file into their machine from a list of zip files on a network path location.
- Developed a console app on C# where search inside of a directory and finds PDFs base on last month and move them to a specific location.
- Developed an ASP.NET MVC Website where it shows a picture of a scanned check from a specific path based on an account number.
- Developed small ASP.NET Web API Controllers for implementation of service layer.
- Developed a WinForms program in C# that increase productivity by 45% by allowing the IT Department to add, modify and search printer's information on a SQL Server Database, also will send an automatic email for additional toners based on the printer's model.
- Increase company user's searches by 30% by developing an ASP.NET website where it searches for Windows Active Directory Users and update a DataGrid with the information obtained so users can look for any employee on the Intranet.
- Developed a program in C# allowing the IT Department to resolve regular open tickets, it increases their productivity by 45%.
- Developed a visual interface program in C# allowing the Collection Department to search an account and based on the State, creates a PDF with the customer information, with the option of print it, this increases their productivity by 85% daily.
- Developed a console program in C# where it searches for pictures files inside of a folder and moves it to a new location.
- Utilize Microsoft Active Directory (AD) to manage objects, users, and groups, assist with software updates including configuring, testing and deploying.

KEY PROJECTS

Final Project, USF

January 2020 - March 2020

- Developed with a team of students a Disaster Management website where will be the point of contact of users in case of a disaster.
- Programmed visual interface using .Net Core MVC and back-end in C# using Visual Studio 2019.
- Created the database using SQL Server and connection with the project using Entity Framework.
- Major functionalities are Login and Register Forms using Identity, Adding User, showing different pages based on Roles,
- It includes a geolocation API, subscription alert system, links to helpful organizations, and live twitter feed from organizations
- Implemented on the website: Razor Engine, Dependency Injection, Google API, Restful API calls (Twilio and SendGrid), jQuery, Vanilla JavaScript
- Completed website called "SimplyHelp"

Independent Study Project, USF

May 2019 – August 2019

- Developed a program where a user search for a company and will display that company information.
- Programmed visual interface and back-end in C# using Visual Studio 2017 and SQL Server (over 1000 lines of code).
- Completed program called "CMS Lookup" now used daily by Mid Atlantic Company Marketing Department employees.